Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1956- 1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
/4139
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3108313
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4108: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4172: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Miller, J. Gormly; Harper, Shirley; Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library --Administration.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
3108313
- CU Requisitions, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Libraries RLG/RLIN Charges Requisitions 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dialog Information Services Requisitions 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- CU Requisitions, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence Administrative Management Society, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence American Library Association, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence American Management Association, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- American Society for Personnel Administration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence Arno Press Inc., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence Bledsoe, William, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence California, University of (Berkeley), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence California, University of (Los Angeles), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence Columbia University, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence Chicago. University of, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence Conference Board, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence Duplicating Products of Ithaca, Inc., 1967-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- General Correspondence Empire State College Associate Degree Program, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- General Correspondence Gaylord Brothers, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- General Correspondence Harvard Business Review, 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence Harvard University Press, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- General Correspondence Hawaii, University of, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- General Correspondence Illinois, University of, 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence International Labour Office, 1959-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- General Correspondence Iowa, University of, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- General Correspondence Michigan State University, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence National Science Foundation, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence National Technical Information Service Deposit Acct. 91962-1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence New York State Library-General, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence New York City- Dept. of Labor, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence New York State Labor Relations Board, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence Nijhoff, Martinus, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Organization Resources Counselors, Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence Taminent Institute and Library See Special Collections-Rand School of Social Science, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government Civil Service Commission, 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence U.S. Department of Labor Library, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government National Labor Relations Board, 1956-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence U.S. Government Social Security Administration, 1969-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence United Transportation Union, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- General Correspondence West Publishing Company, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- General Correspondence Wisconsin, University of, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- General Correspondence Wisconsin State Historical, 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- General Correspondence World Federation of Trade Unions, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- General Correspondence XCP, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence Xerox Corporation, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- CU Payments, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- CU Payments, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- CU Payments, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cornell University Libraries RLG-RLIN Charges - 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cornell University Libraries RLG-RLIN Charges Requisitions 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cornell University Libraries RLG-RLIN Charges - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Stores Enterprises Requisitions 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Cornell Univ. Stores Enterprises, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Ebsco - Requisition - 1986 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Ebsco - Requisitions - 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Ebsco Subscription Service, 1980-83 Requisitions, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Input Culture Company 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Vouchers, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Vouchers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Vouchers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Vouchers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Vouchers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Vouchers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)